unexplainablestore.com 2015-11-01

# Unexplainable Store Privacy Policy

Unexplainablestore.com is very serious about protecting and safeguarding your privacy while navigating our website. We do not want to make your personal data vulnerable and this is why we have created this Privacy Policy. 

Along with our terms and conditions page, our Privacy Policy explains how we handle your personal data once we collect it from you or when you voluntarily offer it to us. This Privacy Policy can be changed any time without a notice. As we reserve the right to alter our Privacy Policy page at any given time, we encourage you to review it often.

**Data We Gather**  
Collecting and processing data about you is part of running our website in a manner that you will like. The information we collect include the following:

  1. The visits we get from our potential customers. We collect details about their domain name and IP address (where possible)
  2. Data that you leave behind when you fill our empty website forms. It could be our newsletter subscribing form, membership sign up form or contact support form
  3. Aggregate information on what pages you access or visit
  4. Information that you give us when you are inquiring about something from us

**Cookies**  
Unexplainablestore.com uses cookies on an occasional basis when it needs to gather data on customers’ computers in order to come up with statistics that would attract advertisers.  
We never identify you specifically when creating our statistical data about the behavior of our customers on our site. We just want to know how you tracked our site, which pages you browsed on our site, from which geographical location you browsed our site, and related stuff. Unexplainable Store does not identify any personal detail about you in its statistics.  
Cookies are automatically downloaded to the computer/laptop you are using with the help of a cookie file that is stored on the hard drive. Once we take this information we use it to make suitable changes to our site so that we can offer you improved services.   
Your computer is able to decline cookies from websites. There is a setting on your browser that can enable you to stop websites from depositing cookie files on your hard drive. Although this sounds good, we would like you to know that using our website while your cookies setting is disabled will be annoying, as access to some parts of our site may be denied.  
We also want to point out that our advertisers may use cookies that we have no control of. Such cookies, if used, would automatically be downloaded to your computer when you click on our website adverts.

**How We Treat Your Information**

**Use:** we primarily use your personal data to improve our site services. We may also use the information we collect in the following ways:

  1. To improve the content of our Web page. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  2. To give you information that you have requested regarding our products and services.
  3. To give you information about other products that we think might interest you as long as you have agreed to it.
  4. To let you know about the changes we make to our site including service/product changes or improvements that may alter how we operate for a while.
  5. To fulfill our obligations concerning the contractual commitments we have with you.

**Sharing:** we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your Personal Identifiable Information to outside parties without your consent, except as noted below:  
We may share your personally identifiable information with trusted third-party business partners for the purpose of operating our website and servicing you, but may not use it for other purposes.  
If we feel that some goods and services from others may be of interest to you, we may send you their information by email. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please contact us and let us know.

**Ad Servers**   
We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

**Access To Your Own Information**   
It is your right to access the data we have stored about you. But you may need to contact us first.

**Contact US**   
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. If there is any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may send us an email at support@unexplainablestore.com, or open a ticket on our [Contact Page](http://www.unexplainablestore.com/contact.php). Our postal address is:

PO Box 803338 #91747

Chicago, IL 60680-3338
